Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Misc. Periodicals and Clippings, undated; 200741
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208287 (Box 45)
    Cheri Samba, Chritiane Richter, Teresa Serrano, Salomé, Castelli, Graciela Hasper, Adriana Varejao, K.H. Hodicke, Maurizio Pellegrin, Peter Schuyff Monika Bravo, Abraham David Christian,
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208289 (Box 46)
    Roger Welch, Lucia Warck Meister, Arturo Duclos, Sabina Mirri, Janieta Eyre, Pizzi Cannella, Nunzio, Jeff Wall, Chuck Connelly, Anna Papratti, Miscellaneous Publications
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 208290 (Box 47)
    Miscellaneous Publications
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 206771 (Box 11)
  - [Concept Image Acoustique], 1996; 210120 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Format: Compact disks.
    Disk was loose with miscellaneous artist publications. Moved to separate box for preservation.
- Oversize Series II: Correspondence, 1981, 2001-2002; 209552
  - Oversize Subseries A: General Artist Files, 209648
    - E, undated; 209647 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Note: There is no Folder 1 for box 53. Folder 2 is the first folder.
    - Steve Shane, 2001-2002; 209646 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Oversize Subseries C: Museums and Universities, 210098
    - Lannan Foundation, undated; 210100 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1982; 210122 (Folder 11)
  - Oversize Subseries D: Art Fairs/Auction Houses, 209553
    - Young Miami, undated; 209554 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Documenta: "FIAC 90-1991", undated; 209645 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Gudaljar: "Venezia Biennale [...]", undated; 209644 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby's: "[Untitled]", undated; 209643 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Basel Art Fari - June 1994/95[99], 210123 (Folder 10)
  - Oversize Subseries E: Magazines, Critics, and Curators, 209555
    - Artforum, undated; 209556 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Art in America, undated; 209557 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - D, 1981; 209558 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series III: Artist Files, 1969, 1980-1999; 209559
  - Oversize Subseries A: General Artist Files, 209560
    - Sandro Chia, undated; 209561 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Julio Galan - Press Articles, undated; 209562 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Vincent Gallo - Press Original [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], undated; 209564 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Piero Gilardi, undated; 209565 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - K.D. Hodicke, 1983; 209566 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Massimo Kaufman, 1988; 209567 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Gary Lang, 1990; 209568 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Sabina Mirri, undated; 209569 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Olivier Mosset, 1969; 209570 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Stephen Mueller [1], 1990; 209571 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Shirin Neshat [1/2], 1995; 209572 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Mimmo Paladino, 1980; 209573 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Rammellzee, 1984; 209574 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Lia Rumma, 1980; 209575 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - [Loose Material from "Salome and Castelli" Letter Box], 1982; 209576 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box], 1981; 209577 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - John Ahearn, 1983; 209642 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Jean-Michel Alberola, 1983; 209641 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Ghada Amer, 1997; 209640 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [Basquiat], 1981, 1982; 209639 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Jose Marie Bermejo, 1980-1984; 209638 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Francois Boisrond, 1984; 209637 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Nancy Bowen - Press, 1985; 209636 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - David Bowes - Press + Correspondence, 1984; 209635 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Beth Brenner, 1988; 209634 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - C, 1981, 1983; 209633 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Pizzi Cannella - Correspondence, 1992; 209632 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Bruno Ceccobelli [2], 1991; 209631 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Chuck Connelly, 1982, 1986-1987; 209630 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Chuck Connelly - Press [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1984; 209629 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - G, undated; 209628 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - $$ Julio Galan Accounting, undated; 209627 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Vincent Gallo [Folder from "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1999; 209626 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - B [Mike Glier] [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated; 209625 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - I/J, 1981-1983; 209624 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder] [1], 1985; 209623 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Barbara Kruger [1/2], 1983, 1984; 209622 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Barbara Kruger - Press [2/2], 1986; 209621 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Barbara Kruger - Reviews, undated; 209620 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Correspondence, undated; 209619 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Press, undated; 209618 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Allan McCollum, 1987, 1988; 209617 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Hanging Instructions for Allan McCollum "200 Plastic Surrogates", undated; 209616 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Keith Milow, 1987; 209615 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - [Shirin Neshat - Anouncements], 1997; 209614 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Donald Newman, 1982; 209613 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Claudio Palmieri, 1986, 1987; 209612 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box], 1981; 209611 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Teresa Serano, 1994-1995; 209610 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Randy Stevens, 1982; 209609 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Adriana Varejao, 1994; 209608 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Tod Wizon, 1984-1987; 209607 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Veronique Bellavista, undated; 210099 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Mike Glier - Downstairs [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated; 210101 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box #2], 1981-1983; 210102 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - S [Mike Glier] [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated; 210103 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lynn Hirshman [Letter Box], undated; 210104 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Barbara Kruger Announcements, 1982-1986; 210105 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Mueller [2], 1986, 1993; 210106 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - David Salle, 1979-1982; 210107 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Cheri Samba, 1991; 210108 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Suzanne Santoro, undated; 210109 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Mario Schifano, undated; 210110 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box], 1980, 1981; 210111 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Jenny Watson, 1991; 210112 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Ellen Brooks [2], undated; 210124 (Folder 1 Left)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box], 1981-1983; 210125 (Folder 9)
    - E. Mattacci, 1983; 210126 (Folder 8)
  - Oversize Subseries E: Material Separated from Visuals Binders, 209601
    - Fernando Canovas [From Front Pocket], undated; 209606 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 6/28], undated; 209578 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 7/28], undated; 209579 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 8/28], undated; 209580 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gian Marco Montesano [From Binder Sleeve 8/8, undated; 209582 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo, undated; 209605 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Back Pocket], undated; 209604 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Front Pocket], undated; 209603 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Front Pocket], undated; 209602 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Back Pocket], undated; 210113 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Fabian Burgos/Graciela Hasper, undated; 210114 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Oversize Series IV: Jean-Michel Basquiat Artist File, undated; 209583
  - Oversize Subseries A: Artist Files, 209649
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Press, undated; 209650 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries C: Accounting, 209584
    - [Contents of Plastic Sleeve from "Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [1/3]"], undated; 209585 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries J: Periodicals Clippings, 209586
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [1/3], undated; 209587 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [2/3], undated; 209588 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [3/3], undated; 209589 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [1/3], undated; 209651 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [Oversive Periodicals] [2/3], undated; 209652 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [3/3], undated; 209653 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series V: Exhibition Records, undated; 210036
  - Subseries A: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; 1982-1983, 1983-1984, 210037
    - [Barbara Kruger], undated; 210038 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Oversize Series VI: Other Administrative Files, undated; 209654
  - Oversize Subseries C: Gallery Space, 209655
    - [530 West 22nd Street Gallery Floor Plan], undated; 209656 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Oversize Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, 1981-2004; 209590
  - Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca] [Oversize] [1/2], 1992, 1999; 209591 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - [Arturo Duclos], 1995; 209592 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Julio Galan [Folder "Mastering Millenn. May 9-Aug 9 1999], 1992-1999; 209593 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Kocheisen + Hullman [Oversize] [1/2], undated; 209594 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - [Myriam] Laplante, undated; 209595 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Helmut Middendorf, 1989, 1991; 209596 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Mirri, 1983, 1984; 209597 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - [Manuel Ocampo], 1994; 209598 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - [Petery Schyff], 1987; 209599 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [1/4], undated; 209600 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Appel; Bowes; Bowen; Pierre; Milow; Abor. Art, [Colombo, Deutsch], 1985; 209657 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - E. Brooks, 1987; 209658 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Julio Galan, 1989; 209659 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Kocheisen + Hullman [Oversize] [2/2], 2003, 2004; 209660 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - [Poster Interleaved in "Ein Anders Klima/A Different Climate" in [?] Folder], undated; 209661 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Samba, 1990-1992; 209662 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [2/4], 1981; 209663 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [3/4], 1988, 1996; 209664 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [4/4], undated; 209665 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Tsibi Geva, 2005; 210115 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Sandro Chia, 1979; 210116 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Liliana Porter, 1991-2003; 210117 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications], undated; 210118 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca], undated; 210127 (Folder 7)
  - Kruger, undated; 210128 (Folder 6)
- Accretion 2011 - Series I: Transaction Records, 1983-2003; 209085
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries A: Consignment Files, 209086
    Chronological
    - In on Consignment Returned 1989, 1987-1989; 209994 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - In on Consignment Returned 1990, 1989-1993; 209990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Out on Consignment Returned 1990, 209992 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - In on Consignment Returned 1991 & 1992, 209993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - In on Consignment 1991-92-93, 1991-1996; 209995 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Consignments, 1996-2003; 210006 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Old Consignments, 1997-2003; 210007 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries F: Artist Books, 209983
    - Post Sales - Records Works Sold in Prince Street in the 1980s, 1983-1985; 209984 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      This folder contains loose leaf sheets with the same information that might be found in an Artist Book (what works by what artists are sold to what collectors, galleries, etc.).
- Accretion 2011 - Series II: Correspondence, 1980-2005; 209980
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries D: Art Fairs/Auction Houses, 209999
    - Young Miami, 2004; 210000 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries E: Magazines, Critics, and Curators, 209981
    - E-Bay, 1989; 210008 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Includes an invitation to Kim Leven to attend the opening of a Julio Galan show.
    - Ads, 2004, 2005; 209982 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Includes some material that could be Series I Subseries A, Series II Subseries C, and Series VI Subseries A.
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries F: Misc. Accretion Correspondence, 210012
    This subseries was created for some accretion correspondence that was neither originally organized as nor fits in any of the Subseries A-E under Series II.
    Chrono
    - Fine Art Conservation Inc., 1980-1983, 1990-1991, 2004; 210013 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [Letter from Chicago Clearing Corporation], 2005; 210014 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Accretion 2011 - Series III: Artist Files, 1999, 2005; 210002
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries A: General Artist Files, 210003
    Alphabetical by folder label
    - British Artists, 1999; 210009 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      Includes material on the artist David Perry and correspondence regarding some damaged prints by Lucia Pearsey.
    - [Loose Material - List of Gallery Artists], undated; 210010 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Artist's Bios, 2005; 210004 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Accretion 2011 - Series V: Exhibition Records, 1980-2004; 209978
  The folders in this accretion series and subseries are placed here by the archivist; they were not received in binders as were the first accession fo Exhibition Records. On examining the contents of each folder the archivist determined that the contents of each seemed to fit in with the material in Series V.
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries J: Accretion Exhibition Records, 209979
    - Press Releases, 1980-1984; 209987 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Price Lists 1980; 1984-1986-87, 1980-1987; 209997 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Press Release 1984-1986-1987, 1983-1987, 1993; 209991 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Group Shows, 1985-2002; 209986 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Group Shows, 1991-1999; 210005 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Photography Show 12/99, 1997-2000; 209996 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Magiciens de la Terre [1/2], 1998; 209988 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Magiciens de la Terre [2/2] [Binder and Contents of Front and Back Pockets], undated; 209989 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Dec. 16th Show w/Richard M.; Group/Winter, 2000-2001; 209985 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - [July 11-October 15, 2002 Group Exhibition Checklist], 209998 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Robert Miller Gallery Nov 2003 Rosenquist Show, 2003-2004; 210001 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Cocktail Party - Bronx Museum, 2005; 210011 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Accretion 2011 - Series VI: Other Administrative Files, 1992-2000; 209083
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries B: Memos, 209084
    - Memos [Loose Material from 1994-1995 Folder], undated; 210015 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Memos [Jan 24, 1992 - May 13, 1994]], 1992-1994; 210016 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Memos [May 27, 1994 - Sep 30, 1994], 210017 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Memos [Jan 7, 1995 - June 23, 1995], 210018 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Memos [June 30, 1995 - Mar 19, 1996], 1995-1996; 210019 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Memos [Apr 4, 1996 - Oct 29, 1996], 210020 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Memos [Nov 5, 1996 - Feb 18, 1997], 1996-1997; 210021 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Memos [Feb 25, 1997 - June 18, 1997], 210022 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Memos [July 7, 1997 - Dec 16, 1997], 210023 (Box 56 a, Folder 1)
    - Memos [Jan 13, 1998 - May 14, 1998], 210024 (Box 56 a, Folder 2)
    - Memos [May 19, 1998 - Dec 17, 1998], 210025 (Box 56 a, Folder 3)
    - Memos [Jan 12, 1999 - Oct 12, 1999], 210026 (Box 56 a, Folder 4)
    - Memos [Oct 19, 1999 - Mar 14, 2000], 1999-2000; 210027 (Box 56 a, Folder 5)
    - Memos [Mar 21, 2000 - Dec 12, 2000], 210028 (Box 56 a, Folder 6)
- Accretion 2011 - Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 209976
  - [Barbara Kruger] [1/3], undated; 210029 (Box 56 b, Folder 7)
  - [Barbara Kruger] [2/3], undated; 210030 (Box 56 b, Folder 8)
  - [Barbara Kruger] [3/3], undated; 210031 (Box 56 b, Folder 9)
  - [Barbara Kruger Reviews Clippings], undated; 210032 (Box 56 b, Folder 10)
  - [Federico Uribe Clippings Book], undated; 210033 (Box 56 b, Folder 11)
- Accretion 2011 - Oversize Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated; 209977
  - [Barbara Kruger], undated; 210035 (Box 54, Folder 16)